Narrator: Ways of moving
Move slowly
M: ambled
Narrator: 2
M: mooched
Narrator: 3
M: wandered
Narrator: 4
M: trudged
Narrator: 5
M: strolled
Narrator: Move quickly
F: sped
Narrator: 7
F: rush
Narrator: 8
F: tore
Narrator: 9
F: dashed
Narrator: 10
F: sprinted
Narrator: Move with confidence or attitude
M: stormed
Narrator: 12
M: strutted
Narrator: 13
M: marched
Narrator: 14
M: swaggered
Narrator: 15
M: strode
Narrator: Move quietly or secretively
F: crept
Narrator: 17
F: slipped
Narrator: 18
F: sneak
Narrator: 19
F: skulking
Narrator: 20
F: tiptoed
Narrator: Move with difficulty
M: staggered
Narrator: 22
M: limped
Narrator: 23
M: hike
Narrator: 24
M: scrambled
Narrator: 25
M: waded
Narrator: Move like an animal
F: waddled
Narrator: 27
F: trotted
Narrator: 28
F: prowled
Narrator: 29
F: scampered
Narrator: 30
F: padded